Wow, you sure have thick eyebrows, Mugi-chan!
ムギちゃんって まゆ毛 太いよね
Yes. But they're actually--
ええ 実はこれ たくあんなの
--takuan pickles!
Wow, they're delicious!
ウマイ！
What's delicious?
何が？
Takuan...
たくあん
A priest?
和尚？
Looks like your fever's still really high...
まだ熱 下がってないんだね
あッ そうか 私 かぜを…
Oh, that's right. I have a bad cold. Achoo!
Ui!
憂～ッ
Here. Blow.
はい チーンして
>_<
Thanks a lot, Ui...
ありがとう 憂
I'll let the school know that you're sick.
学校には連絡しておくから
I'm sorry...
ごめんね
You'd better hurry up, you're gonna be late.
遅刻しちゃうよ 憂
うん
Oh, there's ice cream and mandarin orange jelly in the fridge.
冷蔵庫に アイスとみかんゼリーあるから
Wow, you left me a feast! Thanks a lot, Ui...
大盤ぶるまいだ～ ありがとう
If you need anything, call my cell.
何かあったら 携帯ね
うん
Don't worry. I'll be fine.
大丈夫だよ
CHATTING NOW
Chatting Now
ガチでカシマシ　Never Ending Girls' Talk
It's really noisy
Never Ending Girls' Talk
We can't wait until the bell
rings at the end of class
終業チャイムまで待てない
Even if we're late,
leaving early is a
遅刻はしても早退はNon Non Non!
No no!
精一杯Study After School
study
hard
We'll
after
School
ドキドキが止まんない　フルスロットルな脳内
Our hearts won't stop thumping
Our thoughts are going on full throttle
希望·欲望·煩悩　リボンかけて包装
Hope
Desire
Suffering
Wrap them all up with a ribbon
ネタどっさり持ち寄り　New　Type　Version打ち込み
We'll gather lots of data
and put it in a new type version
男子禁制のプリ帳　恋綴った日記帳
We have a photo album without guys
and a diary written with love
スカート丈2cm　詰めたら跳ぶよ
If we cut our skirts
by 2 centimeters,
we can fly
昨日より遠く　おとといよりオクターブ高く
Further than yesterday
We'll reach a higher octave
than the day before
Jumping
now
Jumping Now
ガチでウルワシ　Never Ending Girls' Life
It's beautiful
Never     Ending
Girls'     Life
日々マジ　ライブだし待ったなし
We're looking
forward
to the daily
concert
Even if we
get up early,
going to bed
early is a
早起きしても早寝はNon Non Non!
No no!
Shouting with all
目一杯Shouting　わっしょい
W
e've
got
Hooray
It's splendid
ガチでスバラシ　Never Ending Girls' Song
Never Ending
Girls' Song
午後ティータイムには持ってこい
The afternoon
tea  time
is perfect
Our unrequited
L
O
V
E
will be defeated
片思いでも玉砕でHere we go!
But here we go!
歌えばShining After School
We'll
sing
for
you
After school
So, her fever still hasn't come down...
まだ 熱 下がらないんだ
No. She'll probably have to stay home tomorrow, too.
うん あの調子だと 明日も多分…
There's only four days left...
残り４日か
I'd gladly trade places with her if I could. By getting her cold to move to me.
私が代わってあげられたらいいのにな
かぜ うつしてもらって
How would you move her cold to you?
うつすって どうやって？
I don't know. Oral transmission?
それは… 口移しとか
She's daring...
大胆な子…
Greetings!
たのもう！
Don't spook the underclassmen!
下級生を ビビらせるなッ
Finale
K-ON!
She is?
そうか
No excuse!
まったく
Getting sick at a time like this just shows her lack of dedication!
こんなときにかぜひくなんて
たるんでる証拠だ
お前がうつしたんだろ
You're the one who gave it to her!
Huh? Oh, I did?
えッ 私？
Yes, you did! I mean look at the timing of it!
そうですよ 時期的に考えても
あッ でも多分
She probably caught it the other day...
A Few Days Ago
こないだ…
I want you to pick your stage outfits from these!
この中からステージ衣装選んで
えッ 強制かよ
You're forcing us to?!
When did she have time to make all these?
いつの間にこんな…
Pick anything you like!
どれでもいいわよ～
How about this waitress outfit, isn't it cute?
たとえば このウエートレス
What can I get for you today?
いらっしゃいませ～
No way!
絶対やだ！
That's even worse!
もっとやだ
That's... not bad, actually.
こッ これはアリか… な
Miss Yamanaka, I think I'm really starting to enjoy this.
先生 なんだか楽しくなってきました
Isn't it fun?
でしょう？
[ When did our calling? ]
戻ってこーい
You guys, look at this!
ねえ 見て見て
Hey, how about we all wear these?
これ どうですか？
These are so cute!
これ かわいいよーッ
Oh, they are! They look easy to move in, too!
本当ね 動きやすそうだし
I guess these aren't so bad.
まあ これなら…
C'mon, these are great! Let's wear these!
ねえねえ これにしようよ～ しようよ～ しようよ～
Let's wear these! Let's wear these! Let's wear these...
Sis was crazy about her yukata.
お姉ちゃん すごく気に入ってて
So much so that she wore hers all day long, and that might be the reason why she caught a bad cold.
そのあと 一日中 浴衣で過ごしてたから
冷えちゃったのかも
What is she too.
小学生か
Sounds like Yui-senpai, all right.
唯先輩らしいですね
Yeah, well, I gotta admit that at the time I was thinking that those outfits were pretty awesome, too.
つーか あのときの衣装もさ
イケてるような気がしたけど…
You know, when you think about them rationally, they're actually kind of embarrassing.
冷静になって考えたら 恥ずかしいですよね
You agree, Mio?
なあ 澪
Azusa. Would you mind practicing all the lead guitar part starting today?
梓 今日からリードの練習もしておいてくれないか
えッ？
You think that Yui might not get better in time?
唯が間に合わないかもしれないってことか？
But I...
でも…
Look, it's just so we can be prepared for the worst.
あくまで万が一に備えてだから
See you after school.
じゃあ 放課後
Later.
じゃあな
I'm sorry...
ごめんね
ううん
Seconds, please...
おかわり
I'm home.
ただいま
Oh, poor Sis...
お姉ちゃん…
Yum!
ウマイ～
The Next Day
Azusa, can you handle it?
梓 いけそう？
Yes, I think so.
はい なんとか
All right. Then, let's run through it one more time from the top.
じゃあ もう１回 最初から通してみようか
Sure.
はい
Hey there!
やっほ～
Ah, you're here!
おッ 来た
Senpai!
先輩
Are you over your cold?
かぜ 大丈夫なの？
Huh? My cold?
あッ かぜか…
That's awfully forced...
わざとらしい
Well, I guess that means you're feeling fine, then.
まあ それなら大丈夫ってことか
If you were feeling better, then you should've come into school this morning!
ていうか 治ったんなら朝からちゃんと来いよ
All of us were pretty worried about you!
みんな心配してたんだぞ
Huh? Oh, that! Right!
えッ？ ああ それは…
そう 授業が終わる頃に 急によくなったの
I suddenly felt better after classes had already ended!
You just wanted to skip school.
サボりたかっただけだろ
That's not important, let's just start practicing, right?
それより 早く練習しましょう
ねッ？
えッ？ そッ そうだね
Yeah, sure, why not.
ジャーンっと…
How's that?
Huh?
あれ？
What do you think?
どう思う？
I'm not certain, but...
わからないけど
Maybe it was just a fluke.
たまたまじゃないか？
Maybe you're right.
Let's try it one more time.
気のせいか…
もう１回やってみよう
I agree.
そうね
Yui...
唯…
Yes?
はい
Our sound is way too tight! It's never ever felt like that before!
完璧に合いすぎるッ
今まで こんな感触なかったのに
All of a sudden, you're playing way too on the beat! What happened?
唯のリズムキープが正確すぎるんだ
何があった？
Not a thing!
なッ 何も…
The moon's turned to blood...
月が赤い
So, what's the problem? If our sound is tight, that's a good thing!
いいじゃないですか
完璧に合っているなら それで
If you ask me, that's the best we've ever played.
私は すごく気持ちよかったです
そうそう
Yeah, yeah! I think we should listen to Azusa!
梓ちゃんの言うとおりだよ
えッ？
Guess you're right.
そうよね
I suppose we were just thrown for a loop.
何か混乱しちゃってたよ
Miss Ritsu, you and Miss Tsumugi just worry too much.
律さんも 紬さんも心配しすぎだよ
Miss Ritsu?
律さん？
Miss Tsumugi?
紬さん？
It's time you dropped the masquerade... Ui-chan.
いいかげん いいんじゃない？
憂ちゃん
When did you--?!
いたのかよ …って
Ui-chan?!
憂ちゃん!?
You may be able to fool others, but you can't fool me.
みんなの目はごまかせても 私の目はごまかせないわよ
Your boobs are bigger than Yui-chan's!
唯ちゃんより オッパイ大きいじゃない
I-I haven't the slightest idea what you're talking about!
なッ 何のことやら さっぱりわかりません
Okay, call me by my nickname, then.
じゃあ 私のあだ名 言ってみて
You, got, Azusa #2!
あッ あずさ２号
あッ ニセモノだ
An imposter!
I'm so sorry.
ごめんなさい
Well, I have to admit you were a dead ringer for Yui. I had no idea.
それにしても似てたな
まったく気づかなかった
I didn't know that you could play the guitar, Ui-chan.
でも 憂ちゃん ギターできたのね
I can't. But Sis let me hold it a few times.
いえ お姉ちゃんに何回か触らせてもらって
Oh, I see, so that's how you play it!
へえ～ そうやって弾くんだ
Yeah, It's written right here!
書いてあるよ ここに
Why am I not surprised?
さもありなん
You know, we might be better off if Yui just stayed home and we let Ui play.
このまま唯には休んでおいてもらった方がいいのかも
Ritsu.
おい
I should apologize to you, too.
梓ちゃんも ごめんね
Sure.
あッ うん
See, when I saw my sister lying there in bed, I couldn't just stand there and do nothing.
なんか ベッドで寝てるお姉ちゃん見てたら
いてもたっても いられなくなっちゃって
Hey there...
やっほ～
Oh, serious deja vu!
うおッ 激しくデジャブ
Senpai!
先輩
Sorry I made you guys worried about me.
ごめんね 心配かけて
Are you feeling better?
大丈夫なの？
I am! When I woke up a little while ago, I was feeling a lot better than before.
うん さっき起きたらね
なんか元気になっててね
I'd hoped to get in a little practice--
少しは練習し…
Gross!
きたね～
Honest, I'm all better!
だから もう大丈夫
You're a liar.
嘘つけ
I need a tissue, too.
あッ 私にもティッシュ
Ah, Geeta!
あッ ギー太！
So that's where you've been!
こんなところにいたのか
Come here! Oh, you're heavy...
よっこいしょ… って重ッ
Oh, Sis!
お姉ちゃん！
Let me make chicken soup with them next time...
今度 お茶漬けにさせてね
えッ？
Hey, your fever hasn't gone down at all!
…熱 全然下がってないじゃないか
I'm sorry...
ごめんね
I guess I won't make it.
やっぱりダメだね
Maybe you'd all be better off playing without me.
私抜きで本番の方がいいかも
Nonsense!
そんな…
Azu-nyan, you take lead guitar for me, okay?
あずにゃん ギターは任せたよ
No way.
いやです
Azusa...
梓ちゃん
I said no! If we all can't play together, I'd rather just cancel the show!
ダメです
みんなでできないのなら 辞退した方がマシです
Azusa, wait!
待った 梓
Yui. Don't come to the club until the show.
唯 本番まで軽音部に来るな
You're kicking me out?
つッ ついに出禁
No.
違う
I'm ordering you to stay home and rest, so you can completely get over your cold.
本番までゆっくり休んで
かぜを完璧に治すこと
そして みんなで本番を迎えること
And then we'll ALL play the show together.
Don't you dare give up until then. Got it?
それまで絶対あきらめるな いいな
Mio-chan...
澪ちゃん
And I want you to practice the lead part, too, Azusa.
梓も ちゃんと練習はしておくように
Not just for when Yui's gone, but for the future of our band.
唯がいなかったときのためじゃなく
今後のために
Senpai...
先輩…
For now, let's do everything we can to get ourselves ready for the show.
今 私達にできる 精一杯のことをやろう
うん
Okay, good night.
じゃあ おやすみ
Good night.
おやすみ
I'm gonna sleep a lot. I'm gonna sleep as much as I can!
いっぱい寝る
今は できるだけいっぱい寝て
I'm gonna get better in time for the show!
絶対 間に合わせる
けいおん！
Yui still isn't here...
唯ちゃん 来ないね
Call her cell?
携帯は？
She sent a message saying that she would be here no matter what.
絶対 間に合わせるってメールは来てたけど
But it's already 12:30.
12時半か
Do you wanna rehearse?
おさらいしておくか
The versions without Yui's parts.
唯抜きの演奏も
I guess we have to.
仕方ないな
No!
いやです
Don't you see we can't do that!
やっぱり いやです
There's no point in practicing if Yui-senpai isn't here with us.
このまま 唯先輩抜きで演奏しても 意味ないです
What's the matter?
どうしたの？
I've pushed back your set 10 minutes, but please be at the auditorium at 1 PM as scheduled.
ステージは10分押しだけど
予定どおり13時には講堂に入って
Understood.
わかった
I see that all club members are present?
全員 そろっているわよね
"Light Music Club: all participants are present and ready"... Good.
軽音部 出演者全員 準備完了… と
Nodoka?
和…
One time...
昔ね…
Oh, no, buckets are full...
もう いっぱいだあ
Yui-chan?
唯ちゃん
We'll use this.
これを使うのだ
Is that really safe?
大丈夫か？
ああ
Yui-chan, it's nice to see you again.
あら 唯ちゃん またまたいらっしゃい
何やてんだよ お前たら
ごめんなさい 健太君
うん
What are we talking about it?
許さん…
健ちゃん？
I'm sorry!
ごめんなさい！
逃げるぞ このバカ
Wait!
待ちなさい！
What the heck?
何だ それ
She's been strange all her life, hasn't she?
昔から変な人だったんですね
But what's the point of that story?
でも 何でそんな話を？
That when Yui is focused on something, she loses sight of everything else.
夢中なことがあると 唯はそれだけしか見えないってこと
I'm sure that she'll forget about her cold. That's why I know she--
きっと かぜのことなんか忘れちゃうわ
だから…
'Sup, girls!
ちょりーッス
Way to ruin the moment!
空気よめ！
More to the point, where the heck have you been?
ていうか 今まで何やってたんだよ
We're having a crisis here!
みんな大変だったのに
Well, I can now show you that I haven't been spending my time doing nothing.
あら もちろんボーッと過ごしていたわけじゃないのよ
I factored in the temperature outside and made the stylish cold-weather version of those yukata!
寒さのことも考えて
あの浴衣の防寒バージョンを作っていたのです
I wish you'd focus that enthusiasm someplace else.
そのやる気を他に回してほしい
And so without further ado!
そして これがその衣装です
うん？
Excuse me for being late...
失礼しまーす
Yui!
唯
You should've come to the club room first!
来てたんなら真っ先に ここに来い
Sorry about that.
ごめんなさい
Azu-nyan?
あずにゃん？
That was so mean! Here we were worried about you, and you...
…最低です
こんなに みんな心配してたのに
It was mean!
最低ですッ
You'd better make amends. Azusa was more worried about you than any of us.
ちゃんと埋め合わせしろよ
梓が一番 心配してたんだから
Huh? She was?
えッ そうなの？
Azu-nyan...
あずにゃん
What you did was terrible!
まったくダメすぎです
For one thing, when you have a cold, you--
大体 かぜをひいたときに…
Glomp!
ギュッ
I didn't mean to worry you. Sorry Azu-nyan.
あずにゃん ごめんね 心配かけて
I'll give it everything I've got. Together with all you guys, okay?
私 精一杯やるよ みんなと一緒に
ねッ
We'll make this the best show ever.
最高のライブにするから
Geez.
もう…
Okay, just this once.
特別ですよ
Now, come on, let's kiss and make up!
仲直り～ッ むちゅちゅッ
You think that Azu-nyan was really worried about me?
本当に私のこと心配してたのかな
I guess.
多分
All right, it's time, girls. Time to get going.
さあ もう時間よ 移動して
Yeah!
オーッ！
Wait a sec. Where's Geeta?
…って あれ？ ギー太は？
I left him here, didn't I?
ここに置いてったよね？
あッ あれ憂ちゃんが持ってかえったぞ
I think Ui-chan took it home with her.
Sis? I'm gonna leave the guitar right here.
お姉ちゃん ギター ここに置いておくね
Sure... Thanks a lot, Ui...
うん ありがとう 憂
Oh my gosh, she did!
What do I do?!
そうだった どうしよう！
Guess we have no choice...
仕方ないわね
Miss Yamanaka?
さわちゃん先生
Here. Use this one.
これ 使いなさい
Do you mind playing a different guitar?
ギー太じゃなくていいのか？
Actually--
ていうか…
I CAN'T play any guitar except Geeta!
ギー太以外のギター 弾けない…
There's a shock...
…だろうな
おっしゃーッ！
わあ すごい
Wow, it's packed already!
もういっぱいだ
I'll just stand.
ここで見てよう
Hi, Ui-chan?
憂ちゃん
Huh? There you are!
あッ 会えた
And now, get ready for a performance by "After-school Teatime" of the Light Music Club.
これより 軽音楽部「放課後ティータイム」による ライブを開始します
Oh, no, where's Sis?
お姉ちゃん
One, two, three!
ワン ツー スリー
My calligraphy pen, fufu
ふでぺんFUFU
is shivering, fufu
ふるえるFUFU
as I write my first greeting card to you.
はじめてキミへのGREETINGCARD
All of my passion
あつめるPASSION
I found it!
あった
and my overflowing actions
あふれてACTION
I have to hurry!
急がなきゃ
might just jut out.
はみ出しちゃうかもね
When I think of your smile,
Come to think of it, I ran down this road the day of the entrance ceremony, too.
そういえば 入学式のときも この道を走った
キミの笑顔想像して　いいとこ見せたくなるよ
I want to show off my good side.
I was thinking, "I've gotta do something!" as I ran.
何かしなきゃって思いながら
Grasping onto my passion,
情熱を握りしめ　振り向かせなきゃ
何をすればいいんだろうって思いながら
I'll have to turn back to you.
And also "What am I going to do?"
And "Is this really how I'm gonna grow up?"
このまま 大人になっちゃうのかなって思いながら
Now it's time to write smoothly with my love.
愛を込めてスラスラとね
さあ　書き出そう
So we can be connected by our happiness
受け取ったキミに
しあわせがつながるように
after you receive it.
The running ink shines until it dries.
走る軌跡　キラキラだね
そう　乾くまで
Wait, calligraphy pen.
まってて　ふでぺん
I'm sorry, ballpoint pen,
ごめんねボールペンは
but you'll have to rest.
おやすみしてて
I'm quite serious.
かなり本気よ★
Listen up, me...
ねえ 私
The me of that day, you don't have to worry.
あの頃の私 心配しなくていいよ
Now it's time to write smoothly with my love.
愛を込めてスラスラとね
さあ　書き出そう
You'll find it soon enough.
すぐ見つかるから
You'll find something that you can do.
私にもできることが
So we can be connected by our happiness
受け取ったキミに
Something that you can lose yourself in.
しあわせがつながるように
夢中になれることが
after you receive it.
I'll show you my dreams as they spin and dance.
夢をみせて　グルグルとね
And a place that...
大切な
A place that...
大切な…
いま　舞い踊る
A place that means more than anything to you!
Hang in there, calligraphy pen.
がんばれふでぺん
大切な場所が
You've done well till now.
ここまできたから
I'm quite serious.
かなり本気よ★
Big Sis!
お姉ちゃん
Oh, Ui!
おお 憂
Peace!
ピース！
Big Sis, you can do it!
お姉ちゃん 頑張って！
Yeah!
おおーッ！
Miss Yamanaka, thanks a lot!
さわちゃん先生 ありがとう
All right, ladies, knock 'em dead.
じゃッ あと頑張りなさい
Miss Yamanaka, you're awesome!
山中先生 カッコいい！
I really am sorry, you guys.
みんな 本当にごめんなさい
Now that I think about it--
よく考えたら
--I'm always causing trouble for you...
いつもいつも ご迷惑を…
And it's always at important times like this!
こんな だいッ 大事なときに…
You should at least tie your tie.
タイくらい ちゃんと結べ
We all think you're the greatest, Yui.
みんな唯が大好きだよ
You can do it, Yui!
頑張って～ッ！
Go get them, Yui!
唯～ッ！
Um, once again, we're After-school Teatime.
えっと 改めまして
放課後ティータイムです
I'm sorry to all of you. I was so late today because I left my guitar at home.
今日は 私がギターを忘れたせいで こんなに遅れてしまいました
Sorry I forgot you, Geeta.
ギー太も忘れて ごめん
That's why?!
それで…
When we started the Light Music Club, we said that our slogan was gonna be "Budokan or bust!"
「目標は武道館」とか言って 私達の軽音部は始まりました
We worked after-school jobs together so I could buy Geeta,
ギターを買うために みんなでバイトしたり
we had tea in the club room together and talked about everything.
毎日 部室でお茶を飲んで たくさんしゃべったり
We had training camps at Mugi-chan's summer house,
ムギちゃんの別荘で合宿したり
and looked for a new student who would join the club.
入部してくれる１年生を探したり
I can't really say that we devoted ourselves wholeheartedly to practicing,
わき目もふらずに 練習に打ち込んできたなんて とても言えないけど
but right now,
でも ここが
for us standing here on the stage,
今いるこの講堂が
this auditorium is our Budokan!
私達の武道館です
And we'll sing our hearts out to the very end!
最後まで思い切り歌います
Fuwa Fuwa Time, guys!
「ふわふわタイム」
キミを見てると　いつもハートDOKI★DOKI
Every time I look at you, my heart starts thumping.
ゆれる思いは　マシュマロみたいに　ふわ★ふわ
The swaying memories are like marshmallows,
light and fluffy.
I'm always doing my best.
いつもがんばる
Always looking at the side of your face.
キミの横顔
ずっと見てても気づかないよね
You haven't noticed, have you?
If it's a dream,
夢の中なら
二人の距離　縮められるのにな
the distance between us will shorten!
あぁカミサマお願い
Dear God,
二人だけのDream Timeください★
please give us the dream time that only belongs to us!
I say good night while hugging my beloved bunny.
お気に入りのうさちゃん抱いて今夜もオヤスミ
Light and fluffy time.
ふわふわタイム
One more time!
もう１回！
Dear God,
あぁカミサマお願い
please give us the dream time that only belongs to us!
二人だけのDream Timeください★
お気に入りのうさちゃん抱いて今夜もオヤスミ
I say good night while hugging my beloved bunny.
Light and fluffy time.
ふわふわタイム
I love light music!
けいおん大好きーッ！
Ritchan, let's do another one!
りっちゃん もう１曲！
You got it!
おっしゃー！
Yui!
唯！
あッ 和ちゃん！
Nodoka-chan!
Your time is up!
もう時間切れよ！
ええーッ！
Huhhhh?
Please
don't say
"you are
lazy,"
Please don't say「You are lazy」
because
I am
actually
crazy
だって本当はcrazy
The swans
are actually
白鳥たちはそう　見えないとこでバタ足するんです
kicking their legs
hard out
of sight
Being true and sincere to my instincts,
I accept that I'll
be tossed around
本能に従順 忠実　翻弄も重々承知
The path ahead looks bright
前途洋々だし…だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
That's why I
take rests
sometimes
近道あればそれが王道　はしょれる翼もあれば上等
If there's a shortcut,
it's the easy way out
If I have wings to use, then it'll be the best
ヤバ 爪割れた　グルーで補修した
Crap, I broke a nail!
I'll fix it with glue
That's enough to give me
a sense of achievement
それだけでなんか達成感
大事なのは自分　かわいがること
What's important is to take good care of yourself
自分を愛さなきゃ　他人も愛せない
If you can't love yourself, then you can't love someone else
Please
don't
say
you
are
Please don't say「You are lazy」
because
you
are
actually
だって本当はcrazy
Capable
hawks
能ある鷹はそう　見えないとこにピック隠すんです
hide their picks
out of sight
I try to use my imagination,
想像に一生懸命　現実は絶体絶命
but reality is a bitch
I'm still just learning,
発展途中だし…だから不意にピッチ外れるんです
so I'll be out of pitch sometimes
Next Episode
マシュマロ豆乳鍋とか チョコカレー鍋とかはどうかな
What about a marshmallow soy milk hot pot or a chocolate curry hot pot?
Let's see...
え～と…
Uh, it's nothing!
何でもない
Check it! Moustache!
ほら ヒゲ
今日は ここで
I have to bow out today.
何か用事？
Do you have plans?
Um, sort of...
うん ちょっと…
Extra
A Winter Day!
Bye!
…じゃあ